// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q001: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Ms. Ortega’s development team contributed ------ to the successful launch of the newest mobile application.',
      choices: ['automatically', 'substantially', 'sharply', 'accordingly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['substantially'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q001',
    },
    {
      question: 'In order to meet production targets, inspection equipment that breaks down easily should be checked on a ------ basis.',
      choices: ['regular', 'regularly', 'regularize', 'regularity'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['regular'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q002',
    },
    {
      question: '------ you experience any problems with the building’s equipment, you should contact the property manager.',
      choices: ['Because of', 'In case of', 'Immediately', 'If'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['If'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q003',
    },
    {
      question: 'Employees must park in the ------ parking lot until the renovation of the company building is completed.',
      choices: ['frequent', 'generous', 'complicated', 'temporary'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['temporary'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q004',
    },
    {
      question: 'Although the assembly machine has been used for more than 20 years, it is still ------.',
      choices: ['annual', 'experienced', 'operational', 'previous'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['operational'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q005',
    },
    {
      question: 'Medical ------ are supposed to investigate the characteristics and effects of newly developed materials.',
      choices: ['expert', 'expertise', 'experts', 'expertly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['experts'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q006',
    },
    {
      question: 'Darwin Construction, renowned for its ------ designs, has won the bid for the Dalton City Library.',
      choices: ['innovation', 'innovate', 'innovatively', 'innovative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['innovative'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q007',
    },
    {
      question: 'Please make sure that ------ address is correct in the designated section of the order form.',
      choices: ['yours', 'yourself', 'your', 'you'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['your'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q008',
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Thompson was ------ as the marketing director after a successful market development in Asia.',
      choices: ['appointing', 'appointed', 'appoint', 'appoints'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['appointed'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q009',
    },
    {
      question: 'The Irwin City Tourist Information Office is ------ located in the center of the city.',
      choices: ['particularly', 'unfortunately', 'absolutely', 'conveniently'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['conveniently'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題001-010/#q010',
    },
  ],
}